SOLD OUT ON YOU
당신은 매진되었습니다
HIT HOMESHOPPING
히트 홈쇼핑
-How many times do I have to tell you? -Sorry, ma'am.
- 몇 번이나 말해야 하나요? -죄송합니다, 부인.
-The product is so good! -Of course!
-제품이 너무 좋아요! -물론!
Dam Ye-jin's a good seller, so tell them to get her!
담예진은 판매력이 좋고, 그러니 그녀를 데려오라고 말해!
They said to change them all to big ones.
다 큰걸로 바꾸라고 하더군요.
Coming through.
통과합니다.
We're up next after Dam Ye-jin, right?
담예진 다음은 우리 차례죠?
Yes, you're up next.
네, 다음은 당신이에요.
Hello, ma'am.
안녕하세요, 부인.
-Sir, you have to check this. -Go do your thing.
- 선생님, 이거 꼭 확인하셔야 해요. -가서 할 일을 하세요.
-Thank you. -Zoom in.
-감사합니다. -확대.
Okay.
좋아요.
We're done preparing the samples.
샘플 준비가 끝났습니다.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
-Hey. -Yes?
-여기요. -예?
Is it always a mess like this in studio?
스튜디오는 늘 이렇게 난리인가요?
Sorry about that, sir.
죄송해요.
Go.
가다.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
It's a complete disaster on set.
세트장에서는 완전한 재앙입니다.
Wait, we're about to go live, but where on earth is Ye-jin?
잠깐만요, 이제 곧 방송이 시작됩니다. 그런데 예진이는 대체 어디에 있는 걸까?
Dam Ye-jin's not picking up.
담예진이 전화를 안 받네요.
What?
무엇?
What did you just say, Ms. Eom?
방금 엄씨, 뭐라고 했어요?
We may have to go on without her.
우리는 그녀 없이 계속해야 할 수도 있습니다.
How can we go live without the main host?
메인 호스트 없이 어떻게 라이브를 할 수 있나요?
I don't know! What do we do?
모르겠습니다! 우리는 무엇을 합니까?
All right, everyone.
좋아요, 여러분.
The product I'll be introducing today
오늘 소개해드릴 제품
is none other than
다음은 다름 아닌
all-purpose gloves for cleaning!
청소를 위한 만능장갑!
Don't they look as adorable as I do?
그 사람들도 나만큼 사랑스러워 보이지 않나요?
Woof, woof!
으윽, 으악!
They're 100% made in Korea. Zero synthetic fibers!
100% 한국에서 만들어졌습니다. 합성섬유 제로!
Perfect for removing stains!
얼룩제거에 딱!
They're powerful!
그들은 강력해요!
Ms. Eom, let's just roll a recorded segment right now.
엄씨, 그냥 굴러가자 지금 녹화된 부분입니다.
If something goes wrong on air, we'll all be done for.
방송에서 무슨 일이 생기면 우리는 모두 끝낼 것입니다.
And that's why…
그래서…
Sir, we'll go straight into the demo.
선생님, 바로 데모로 들어가겠습니다.
We're not getting many calls, so how about starting the demo right away?
전화가 많이 오지 않습니다. 그럼 바로 데모를 시작하는 게 어때요?
Now, I'll demonstrate the power of these all-purpose gloves.
이제 시연해 보겠습니다. 이 다용도 장갑의 힘.
Dust!
먼지!
Oh, my God! Jesus! Now, let's try removing grease!
오, 맙소사! 맙소사! 이제 기름기를 제거해 보겠습니다!
All right!
괜찮은!
All right! Okay! Like this!
괜찮은! 좋아요! 이와 같이!
Okay!
좋아요!
Of course, it's hard to get rid of grease easily.
물론 어렵죠 기름기를 쉽게 제거하기 위해.
You, the floor manager. Come here.
당신, 플로어 매니저. 이리 오세요.
All right!
괜찮은!
Hey, why isn't this coming off?
야 이거 왜 안 나오냐?
You're supposed to wet it first.
먼저 적셔 놓으셔야 합니다.
All right, our final attack! Hey, grease!
좋아, 마지막 공격이다! 이봐, 그리스!
Take this!
이것을 받아라!
Hey, are you okay?
이봐, 괜찮아?
These all-purpose gloves
이 다용도 장갑
may not be that effective, but aren't they charming?
그다지 효과적이지 않을 수도 있지만, 하지만 정말 매력적이지 않나요?
We're losing all the calls!
우리는 모든 전화를 잃고 있어요!
Please do something, Mr. Hwang!
어떻게든 해주세요, 황 선생님!
Well, let's calm down first.
자, 우선 진정하자.
"Calm down"?
"진정하다"?
Does it look like I can calm down?
진정할 수 있을 것 같나요?
I put my faith in Ms. Dam
나는 담 선생님을 믿었어요
and had everyone work overtime for an entire month
그리고 모두들 초과근무를 하게 했어 한 달 내내
to pull together every bit of stock we could!
함께 끌어당기다 우리가 할 수 있는 모든 재고!
Enough. If today's show flops, I'm filing a lawsuit right away.
충분한. 오늘 쇼가 실패한다면, 바로 소송을 제기할 예정입니다.
Ma'am, there's a big problem!
부인, 큰 문제가 생겼어요!
Our sales are a bigger problem. Look.
우리의 매출이 더 큰 문제입니다. 바라보다.
LIVE ORDER STATUS
실시간 주문 상태
Mr. Hwang, you go in and do the demo instead.
황 선생님 들어가세요 대신 데모를 해보세요.
Tell our host to just talk and not do anything else.
호스트에게 그냥 이야기하라고 전해 주세요 그리고 다른 일은 하지 마세요.
What? Me?
무엇? 나?
What?
무엇?
You can't do it? I guess he can't do it.
당신은 그것을 할 수 없습니다? 내 생각엔 그 사람은 할 수 없을 것 같아.
Then, what do we do? I'll go. I can do it.
그러면 우리는 무엇을 할까요? 나는 갈 것이다. 나는 할 수 있다.
Just make quick cuts and flash the "Almost Sold Out" captions.
그냥 빨리 자르세요. 그리고 "거의 매진" 캡션을 깜박입니다.
And we'll all take a trip to the Standards Commission.
그리고 우리는 모두 여행을 떠날 거예요 표준위원회에.
Move!
이동하다!
Let go of me! Let me get on air before they fire me!
날 놔줘! 그들이 나를 해고하기 전에 방송에 나설 수 있게 해주세요!
All right, I'll get on standby!
알았어, 대기할게!
For crying out loud!
큰 소리로 울었기 때문에!
Who is it? Whose phone is ringing when we're live…
누구입니까? 누구의 전화가 울리고 있는가 라이브할 때...
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Okay, stand by.
좋아, 대기해.
Action.
행동.
Everyone, were you looking for me?
여러분, 저를 찾고 계셨나요?
I'm greeting you from a special location today.
나는 당신에게 인사합니다 오늘은 특별한 장소에서.
I'm your home shopping host, Dam Ye-jin.
여러분의 홈쇼핑 호스트 담예진 입니다.
Can you guess where I am?
내가 어디에 있는지 추측할 수 있나요?
I'm at the highest building in Korea,
나는 한국에서 가장 높은 건물에 있어
the Lux Tower.
럭스 타워.
Lux Tower!
럭스 타워!
-She's finally here. -Yeah!
-드디어 왔네요. -그렇습니다!
Why am I here?
내가 왜 여기 있지?
Everyone.
모두들.
-What? -Look here.
-무엇? -여기를 보세요.
-See this window? -This is incredible.
-이 창을 보시겠습니까? -이건 말도 안 돼요.
This is a year's worth of built-up grime!
이것은 1년 동안 쌓인 오물입니다!
It's crazy, right?
미친 짓이군요, 그렇죠?
Ordinary cleaning products won't be able to remove this.
일반 청소용품 이것을 제거할 수 없습니다.
All right. Watch this.
괜찮은. 이것을 보세요.
I'll spray this cleaner.
이 클리너를 뿌리겠습니다.
All right.
괜찮은.
Everyone, do you see this?
여러분, 이거 보이시나요?
I'm wiping pretty hard, but look at how this grime is still there.
열심히 닦고 있는데, 하지만 이 때가 어떻게 아직도 거기에 있는지 보세요.
But now,
하지만 지금은
I'll show you the power of these all-purpose gloves.
당신에게 힘을 보여드리겠습니다 다목적 장갑
All I did was soak these in water, and I wrung them out.
내가 한 일은 이것을 물에 담그는 것뿐이었습니다. 그리고 나는 그것들을 짜냈습니다.
You might wonder, "Did she spray them with bleach or cleaner?"
당신은 "그녀가 그걸 뿌렸나요?"라고 궁금해할 수도 있습니다. 표백제나 세척제로요?"
How nice and damp.
얼마나 좋고 축축한가.
Did you see? There's only water on it. Now, look carefully.
봤어? 그 위에는 물만 있습니다. 자, 주의 깊게 살펴보세요.
Where did it all go?
다 어디로 갔나요?
Everyone, you really have to try this out for yourself.
여러분, 꼭 그렇게 하셔야 합니다 이것을 직접 시도해 보세요.
I'm sure you all know what this is.
이것이 무엇인지 여러분 모두 알고 계실 거라 확신합니다.
Since it lasts even through greasy meals, they call it "paint lipstick."
기름진 식사에도 지속력이 좋기 때문에 그들은 그것을 "페인트 립스틱"이라고 부릅니다.
DAM YE-JIN
담예진
Hey, what are you doing?
이봐, 뭐하는 거야?
Everyone, if I can't erase this,
여러분, 이거 지울 수 없다면
I'm going to get in big trouble.
나는 큰 문제에 빠지게 될 것입니다.
-Will these all-purpose gloves save me? -Geez, this was expensive!
-이 다용도 장갑이 나를 구해줄까요? - 이런, 이거 비쌌어!
Just wait and watch.
그냥 기다려 보세요.
All right.
알았어.
What do you think? It's spotless, isn't it?
어떻게 생각하나요? 흠 하나 없는 곳이죠, 그렇죠?
That is amazing.
정말 놀랍습니다.
Everyone, with these all-purpose gloves, I just got acknowledged
여러분, 이 만능 장갑을 끼고 방금 인정받았어
by a professional building cleaner with 30 years of experience.
전문 건물 청소업체 30년의 경험을 가지고 있습니다.
These gloves will instantly make you a professional cleaner!
이 장갑을 사용하면 즉시 당신을 만들 수 있습니다 전문 청소부
You'll get a 10% discount only during this broadcast,
10% 할인을 받으실 수 있습니다 이 방송 중에만
so place your order now through our mobile app.
지금 주문하세요 모바일 앱을 통해
If I had these, I'd be in the majors.
만약 내가 이걸 가지고 있었다면 나는 메이저에 갔을 것이다.
Hey, they're not those kinds of gloves!
아, 그런 장갑이 아니거든요!
Yes, the all-purpose gloves?
네, 만능장갑요?
They grab every bit of dust and grime there is.
그들은 모든 비트를 잡아 먼지와 오물이 있습니다.
Even fine dust you can't see is all trapped right in here.
눈에 보이지 않는 미세먼지도 모두 여기에 갇혀있습니다.
And it's waterproof inside, so your hands will stay perfectly dry.
그리고 내부는 방수 처리되어 있고, 그러면 손이 완전히 건조한 상태로 유지됩니다.
They're also really easy to clean.
청소도 정말 쉽습니다.
A large size?
큰 사이즈?
If you were worried about getting your hands wet or dirty while cleaning,
받을까봐 걱정되셨다면 청소하는 동안 손이 젖었거나 더러워졌네요
you don't have to worry about that now.
이제 걱정할 필요가 없습니다.
Do you see how nice and dry my hands are?
내 손이 얼마나 멋지고 건조한지 아시나요?
Now,
이제
let me highlight the key features of these all-purpose gloves once more.
주요 기능을 강조하겠습니다 이 다용도 장갑을 다시 한 번 소개합니다.
Yeah, didn't I tell you? You can put your faith in Dam Ye-jin.
응, 내가 말하지 않았어? 담예진씨를 믿으시면 됩니다.
Dam Ye-jin really knew what she was doing.
담예진은 자신이 하는 일을 정말 잘 알고 있었다.
All right, the second set is almost sold out as well.
자, 두 번째 세트 거의 품절도 되네요.
We're probably going to end early.
아마 일찍 끝날 것 같아요.
Make sure the next one's ready.
다음 것이 준비되었는지 확인하세요.
Everyone, this is going to be sold out within one minute.
여러분 이거 가요 1분 안에 매진될 예정입니다.
So hurry. I'll throw it back to the studio now.
그러니 서두르세요. 이제 스튜디오에 다시 던져보겠습니다.
This has been your host, Dam Ye-jin. Thank you!
여러분의 호스트 담예진님이셨습니다. 감사합니다!
Cut!
자르다!
I thought I was going to die earlier!
일찍 죽을 줄 알았는데!
Wait. Hold on.
기다리다. 기다리다.
-Hang on. Let me see. -What is it?
-잠깐만요. 어디 보자. -이게 뭐죠?
Just a moment.
잠시만요.
Please…
제발...
We're completely sold out of today's stock!
우리는 완전히 오늘 재고가 매진되었습니다!
Sold out!
매진!
Everyone, they said we're sold out!
여러분 저희가 매진됐다고 하더군요!
Sold out?
매진되었나요?
Sir!
선생님!
Sold out!
매진!
-Great job! -We're sold out!
-잘했어요! - 매진됐어요!
Sir!
선생님!
-Sold out!
-매진!
Sold out!
매진!
We're sold out!
우리는 매진되었습니다!
Sold out! Thank you!
매진! 감사합니다!
Thank you!
감사합니다!
SOLD OUT ON YOU
당신은 매진되었습니다
DEOKPUNG VILLAGE
덕풍마을
Mechoori, thank you!
메추리님, 감사합니다!
Sorry?
죄송합니다?
Thanks for taking Changsik on a walk.
창식이를 산책시켜줘서 고마워요.
I didn't. He just followed me.
나는하지 않았다. 그는 단지 나를 따라왔다.
CHANGSIK HE DOESN'T BITE
창식 그는 물지 않는다
-And that mutt-- -His name's Changsik.
-그리고 그 멍청이-- - 이름은 창식이에요.
Yes, Changsik. He needs to be put on a leash.
응, 창식아. 그는 가죽 끈을 매야합니다.
He'll grow big enough to high-five you soon.
그 사람은 충분히 성장할 거예요 곧 하이파이브하자.
What? What's that?
무엇? 그게 뭐야?
Well…
글쎄… ​​
It's like patty-cake…
패티 케이크 같아…
Anyway,
어쨌든,
it's dangerous to let him follow anyone around.
그 사람을 놔두는 건 위험해 주변에 있는 사람을 따라가세요.
Come on. What do you mean "anyone"?
어서 해봐요. "누구나"란 무슨 뜻인가요?
Changsik only likes you, Mechoori.
창식이는 메추리 너만 좋아해.
-He does. -Whenever he sees you,
- 그래요. -그가 당신을 볼 때마다
he follows you around!
그 사람이 당신을 따라다닙니다!
-And he follows and follows!
- 그리고 그는 따라오고 또 따른다!
I'm not Mechoori.
저는 메추리가 아닙니다.
What?
무엇?
It's Matthew Lee.
매튜 리입니다.
Right. Matthew…
오른쪽. 매튜…
-Mechoori!
-메초리!
Hey, Mechoori.
안녕, 메추리.
Take these and steam them.
이것을 가져다가 찌십시오.
It's fine. I have a lot of food at home.
괜찮습니다. 집에 먹을 것이 많아요.
Fine, I'll throw them away.
좋아요, 버릴게요.
Okay, fine.
알았어, 알았어.
You're going to eat them?
그걸 먹을 건가요?
This is too much. Do you have some for yourself?
이건 너무해요. 당신을 위한 것도 있나요?
Of course. I have tons left.
물론. 나에게는 톤이 남았다.
All right. Just this once then.
괜찮은. 그럼 이번 한 번만.
Mechoori!
메추리!
-Hey, Mechoori! -Hey. Mechoori!
-야, 메추리! -여기요. 메추리!
Mechoori…
메초리…
NO DATA AVAILABLE
사용 가능한 데이터가 없습니다
NO INPUT SIGNAL
입력 신호 없음
See? It's not working.
보다? 작동하지 않습니다.
The Wi-Fi must be disconnected.
Wi-Fi 연결을 끊어야 합니다.
Why is it so bad?
왜 그렇게 나쁜가요?
Then call your service provider.
그런 다음 서비스 제공업체에 전화하세요.
I'll be already dead by the time they arrive.
난 이미 죽었을 거예요 그들이 도착할 때쯤에는.
-They'll arrive before that. -What?
- 그 전에 도착할 거예요. -무엇?
Mechoori, where are you going?
메추리야, 어디 가니?
Mechoori! Hey!
메추리! 여기요!
Come and sit down.
와서 앉으세요.
Sit down, everyone.
다들 앉으세요.
-Song Ga-in! Song Ga-in!
-송가인! 송가인!
Have a seat.
앉으세요.
Are you here to see Song Ga-in too?
송가인 씨도 만나러 오셨나요?
Come and sit down.
와서 앉으세요.
Geez.
이런.
Is it working?
작동합니까?
Go look.
가서 봐.
No!
아니요!
Move it to the right.
오른쪽으로 이동합니다.
Just a bit more.
조금만 더.
What about now?
지금은 어떻습니까?
BEST TROT SINGER SONG GA-IN
최고의 트로트 가수 송가인
Just a bit more!
조금만 더!
Just a little more.
조금만 더.
And now?
그리고 지금은?
It's working!
작동 중이에요!
It's working now!
지금 작동 중입니다!
DEOKPUNG VILLAGE SENIOR CENTER OPENING
덕풍마을 노인센터 개원
Good job!
잘했어요!
-This is awesome! -It's working really well!
-이거 정말 대단해요! - 정말 잘 작동하고 있어요!
It looks nice and clear.
깔끔하고 좋은 것 같습니다.
Gosh, thank you so much.
이런, 정말 고마워요.
You can head back now.
이제 돌아가셔도 됩니다.
Leave it. I'll put that away.
그대로 두십시오. 그건 치워두겠습니다.
It's fine. And one more thing.
괜찮습니다. 그리고 한 가지 더.
That's the last time I'm going up on the roof.
그게 마지막이야 나는 옥상으로 올라갈 예정이다.
Here…
여기...
I'm off.
나는 떠난다.
-Mechoori!
-메초리!
He's good at driving too.
그 사람 운전도 잘해요.
Look at him.
그를보세요.
He's so prickly.
그는 너무 까칠해요.
He never says yes with a smile.
그는 결코 미소를 지으며 그렇다고 대답하지 않습니다.
That young brat.
그 어린 놈.
Hey, you old brat!
이봐, 이 늙은이!
Even if he speaks curtly, he's been helping us with everything.
퉁명스럽게 말을 해도 그 사람은 모든 일에서 우리를 도와주고 있어요.
You shouldn't treat him like that.
그 사람을 그렇게 대하면 안 돼요.
-He's right! -Yeah!
-그 말이 맞아요! -응!
ONE DAY AT JONG-IL'S COW SHED
어느 날 정일의 외양간에서
One, two, three, pull!
하나, 둘, 셋, 당겨!
Pull!
당기다!
Okay. One, two, three, pull!
좋아요. 하나, 둘, 셋, 당겨!
-The teeth look fine. -That's a relief.
-치아가 괜찮아 보이네요. - 다행이네요.
UNERUPTED TEETH STILL COVERED BY GUMS
깨지지 않은 치아 아직 잇몸에 덮여 있음
That was exhausting, wasn't it?
정말 지치는 일이었죠, 그렇죠?
Mechoori's better than you at pulling calves now.
메추리가 너보다 낫다 지금 송아지를 당기는 중입니다.
Hey, don't be stupid.
이봐, 바보 같은 소리 하지 마
Don't you know how many calves I pulled at your shed?
송아지가 몇 마리인지 모르시나요? 내가 네 창고를 잡아당겼다고?
You don't need to deliver them anymore.
더 이상 배달할 필요가 없습니다.
Mechoori's really come into his own handling them now!
메추리는 정말 자기만의 방식으로 다가왔어 지금 처리하세요!
Geez, do you know why I'm asking Mechoori to pull your calves?
이런, 내가 왜 묻는지 아세요? 종아리를 당기는 메추리?
I pity the calves that will have to see that ugly face of yours their whole lives.
봐야할 송아지들이 불쌍하다 그 추악한 얼굴은 평생 동안.
I wanted to let them see Mechoori's handsome face for a moment.
나는 그들에게 허락하고 싶었다 메추리의 잘생긴 얼굴을 잠시 보세요.
Are you done talking?
얘기 다 끝났어?
Nope, not at all.
아니요, 전혀 그렇지 않습니다.
Have you forgotten when you used to get beaten up
잊어버렸나요 네가 구타당하곤 했을 때
all the time?
항상?
Bring it on then. How about a bull fight?
그럼 가져오세요. 황소싸움은 어때요?
Go ahead.
계속하세요.
This is my last time
이번이 마지막이야
helping you out in the shed.
창고에서 당신을 도와줍니다.
-I'm off. -Thanks.
-나는 간다. -감사해요.
Wait, there's one more!
잠깐, 하나 더 있어요!
Come on! Hurry!
어서 해봐요! 서두르다!
Come here.
이리 오세요.
Damn it.
젠장.
That's not all.
그게 다가 아닙니다.
He even chopped all your firewood for you.
그는 심지어 당신을 위해 장작을 모두 잘랐습니다.
ON ANOTHER DAY, HOUSE CALL FOR FIREWOOD CHOPPING
다른 날, 장작패기 집요일
Geez!
이런!
Please…
제발...
He's right!
그 말이 맞아요!
And you remember that other time?
그리고 저번에 그 일을 기억하시나요?
AND ON ANOTHER DAY, VILLAGE HALL BEEHIVE REMOVAL
그리고 또 다른 날, 마을회관 벌집 제거
Grab the end. It's okay.
끝을 잡아라. 괜찮아요.
-Find your balance. -Don't be scared.
- 균형을 찾으세요. - 겁먹지 마세요.
DEOKPUNG COMMUNITY CENTER
덕풍커뮤니티센터
Yeah, you're right.
그래, 당신 말이 맞아요.
That's right! That day was really fun too.
좋아요! 그날도 정말 즐거웠어요.
AND ON YET ANOTHER DAY, DEOKPUNG VILLAGE'S KIMCHI-MAKING DAY
그리고 또 다른 날, 덕풍마을 김치 담그는 날
Mechoori, open up.
메추리야, 열어라.
"It's Matthew Lee, not Mechoori."
"메추리가 아니라 매튜 리입니다."
And there's that.
그리고 그게 있습니다.
Why aren't you mentioning that?
왜 그걸 언급하지 않는 거죠?
You know. That.
알잖아. 저것.
TYPHOON ROMEO HITS DEOKPUNG VILLAGE
태풍 로미오가 덕풍마을 강타
Oh, come on.
아, 어서.
Damn it.
젠장.
And you still think he's prickly?
그런데 아직도 그 사람이 까칠하다고 생각하시나요?
I do remember something else.
나는 다른 것을 기억합니다.
Our village might fly away at this rate!
이대로 가면 우리 마을이 날아갈지도 몰라!
This is insane.
이건 미친 짓이야.
Come on. Let's close the window.
어서 해봐요. 창문을 닫자.
-Close it. -It's not closing.
- 닫으세요. - 안 닫혀요.
TYPHOON JULIET HITS DEOKPUNG VILLAGE
태풍 줄리엣이 덕풍마을 강타
Come on!
어서 해봐요!
Right!
오른쪽!
We would've been in huge trouble if it weren't for him.
우리 큰일났을텐데 그 사람이 아니었다면.
-But he wasn't like this from the start. -Yeah.
-근데 처음부터 그런 사람은 아니었어요. -응.
He's finally become a bit nice.
드디어 좀 착해졌네요.
What did I tell you?
내가 뭐라고 말했지?
Mechoori's like streusel bread.
메추리는 슈트로이젤 빵과 같아요.
Rough on the outside but soft on the inside.
겉은 거칠다 하지만 속은 부드럽다.
Streusel bread!
슈트로이젤빵!
You're right. Should I go buy some streusel bread?
당신 말이 맞아요. 가서 사야 하나? 슈트로이젤 빵?
-Sounds nice. -How many? Two?
- 좋은 것 같아요. -얼마나? 둘?
DEOKPUNG VILLAGE BUS STOP
덕풍마을 버스 정류장
Mechoori, stop!
메추리, 그만해!
I'm going to get off here!
난 여기서 내릴 거야!
Thanks.
감사해요.
When are you heading back?
언제 돌아가시나요?
I'm not the village bus driver.
저는 마을버스 운전사가 아닙니다.
I'm heading back around 4:30 p.m.
오후 4시 30분쯤에 돌아올 예정이에요.
You can wait for me then or whatever.
그때 아니면 뭐든지 기다려도 돼요.
I said 4:30 p.m., okay?
오후 4시 30분이라고 했는데요, 그렇죠?
Okay, 4:30 p.m. See you later.
알았어, 오후 4시 30분 나중에 봐요.
Bye.
안녕.
A simultaneous live broadcast?
동시 생방송?
You know how Dam Ye-jin is.
담예진이 어떤 사람인지 아시죠?
Once she's set on something, she stops at nothing.
일단 그녀가 뭔가를 시작하면, 그녀는 아무것도 멈추지 않습니다.
My heart was racing, and I was nervous and anxious all morning.
심장이 뛰었다, 그리고 나는 아침 내내 초조하고 불안했습니다.
I'm filing a workers' comp claim!
근로자 보상 청구를 제출하겠습니다!
You have to add my name as well.
내 이름도 추가해야 합니다.
The partner company people threatened to sue me!
협력업체 관계자 고소하겠다고 협박했어요!
-I really-- -Okay, I get it! You did great.
-난 정말-- -알았어, 알겠어! 정말 잘했어요.
Hey, it all ended well today.
안녕하세요 오늘은 모두 무사히 끝났습니다.
You know how intense Dam Ye-jin is.
담예진씨가 얼마나 강렬한지 아시죠?
But what's with her anyway?
그런데 그녀는 대체 왜 있는 걸까요?
I know she's popular, but she's filming commercials…
나는 그녀가 인기가 있다는 것을 안다. 그런데 그녀는 광고를 촬영하고 있어요…
WHETHER IT'S RAIN OR SNOW IONA
비가 오든 눈이 오든 아이오나
She's a brand ambassador,
그녀는 브랜드 홍보대사입니다.
and she's even appearing on Running Man.
런닝맨에도 출연하고 있어요.
What is she even doing on there?
그녀는 거기서 무엇을 하고 있는 걸까요?
What is she going to do? What?
그녀는 무엇을 할 예정입니까? 무엇?
Superstar Dam! Gosh, no need to be sorry!
슈퍼스타댐! 맙소사, 미안해할 필요 없어!
No, it was good!
아니, 좋았어!
Gosh, a true professional would never complain about that…
맙소사, 진정한 전문가 그것에 대해 결코 불평하지 않을 것입니다…
Lunch?
점심?
I'll come by myself.
나 혼자 올게.
Hurry? Okay, I'm coming.
서두르다? 알았어, 갈게.
Are you all right?
괜찮으세요?
Weren't you even scared?
겁도 안 났어요?
Gosh, I'm more afraid of leftover stock.
맙소사, 나는 남은 재고가 더 두렵습니다.
I'm late for an engagement, so I'll get going.
약혼 시간에 늦었어요. 그래서 나는 갈 것이다.
Ye-jin!
예진!
-Hello.
-안녕하세요.
-Could we have an autograph?
-사인을 받을 수 있을까요?
-Thank you.
-감사합니다.
I loved the show.
나는 쇼를 좋아했습니다.
I'm a huge fan. Could I get a photo with you?
나는 엄청난 팬이다. 당신과 함께 사진을 찍을 수 있을까요?
-Thank you.
-감사합니다.
I'm a huge fan.
나는 엄청난 팬이다.
Here's your dish.
여기 당신의 요리가 있습니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Please enjoy.
즐겨주세요.
Lucky you. You always arrive right when the food comes.
행운을 빌어요. 넌 언제나 도착해 음식이 나오자마자.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
But I practically flew over here to see you.
하지만 나는 실질적으로 당신을 만나러 여기로 날아왔습니다.
Eat up.
먹어라.
Let's watch a movie later.
나중에 영화를 보자.
We can go after we eat.
식사 후에 가셔도 됩니다.
You said you wanted to see this.
이거 보고 싶다고 하셨어요.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Our new program's launching tomorrow,
내일 새 프로그램이 시작됩니다.
so I have to head back to work after dinner…
그래서 난 다시 돌아가야 해 저녁 식사 후에 일하러…
You know how many surgeries I do each day?
내가 하루에 몇 번이나 수술을 하는지 아세요?
I'm probably one of the busiest people in Korea.
나는 아마 한국에서 가장 바쁜 사람 중 한 명.
But "busy" is something…
하지만 "바쁘다"는 건...
What's with this knife? It's light.
이 칼은 뭐죠? 가볍습니다.
It cuts well. And it's cute.
잘 잘립니다. 그리고 귀엽네요.
This would be nice for a fancy meal.
고급스러운 식사로 좋을 것 같아요.
Yeah, this is perfect.
그래, 완벽해.
-Are you listening to me? -You pass.
- 내 말 듣고 있어? -합격.
I'm sure our customers would love this.
고객들이 이것을 좋아할 것이라고 확신합니다.
Should I try to sell it?
팔아볼까?
Let's break up.
헤어지자.
Ui-seok, are you angry?
의석아 화났어?
I'll postpone the meeting. Let's go see the movie.
회의를 연기하겠습니다. 영화 보러 가자.
Forget it. You're just going to keep stepping out to take calls.
잊어버리세요. 그냥 가는 거야 전화를 받기 위해 계속 밖으로 나섰습니다.
No,
아니요,
I'll really--
난 정말--
Do you really think this is about me waiting a few minutes?
정말 이것이라고 생각하시나요? 내가 몇 분 정도 기다리고 있다는 얘기야?
What's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
Aside from surgeries, I see about 300 outpatients a day too.
수술 외에도 하루에 외래환자도 300명 정도 봐요.
But do you know why I still make time to date?
그런데 왜인지 아시나요? 난 아직도 데이트할 시간이 있어?
Because I have a personal life.
왜냐하면 나는 개인적인 삶을 살고 있기 때문입니다.
I want to live like a human being.
나는 인간처럼 살고 싶다.
I just want to laugh and enjoy my time with you.
난 그냥 웃고 싶어 그리고 당신과 함께 즐거운 시간을 보내세요.
But with you, Dam Ye-jin. Not home shopping host Dam Ye-jin.
하지만 담예진님과 함께라면요. 홈쇼핑 호스트 담예진이 아닙니다.
But…
하지만…
I can't separate those two that distinctly.
헤어질 수 없어 뚜렷이 구별되는 두 가지.
Then, you can just date that job of yours that you love so much.
그럼 그냥 그 직업이랑 데이트하면 돼 당신이 너무 사랑한다는 것.
The gentleman already paid.
그 신사는 이미 돈을 지불했어요.
Actually, it's not because of that.
사실 그것 때문은 아니다.
Your cutlery…
당신의 식기류...
Could I know who you bought these from?
이거 누구한테서 샀는지 알 수 있을까요?
Hey, Mr. Hwang.
안녕하세요, 황 선생님.
Ms. Dam!
담씨!
You almost made me faint earlier!
아까 나를 거의 기절시킬 뻔했잖아!
I… Oh, my gosh!
난… 아, 맙소사!
Mr. Hwang, I found our next product.
황 선생님, 다음 제품을 찾았어요.
This is cutlery made from premium stainless steel
만든 커트러리 입니다 프리미엄 스테인레스 스틸로 제작
and Nordic wood.
그리고 북유럽 나무.
Both its features and performance are amazing.
두 가지 기능 모두 성능이 놀랍습니다.
Let's test it and get in touch to make it our next product.
테스트해보고 연락하자 다음 제품으로 만들려고요.
Hang on.
잠깐만요.
A Nordic walnut handle that's been oiled twice
북유럽 호두나무 손잡이 기름칠을 두 번이나 했어
and intricately carved to a 1.5mm thickness…
그리고 복잡하게 조각된 1.5mm 두께로…
I can just tell how well it'll cut.
얼마나 잘 자르는지 알 수 있어요.
Let's do it!
해보자!
-All right!
-괜찮은!
Okay. All right, then.
좋아요. 그럼요.
I'll wait in the lobby.
로비에서 기다릴게요.
Don't be late.
늦지 마세요.
JI YUN-JI HIT'S TOP SELLER FOR 2024
지윤지 2024년 히트작 최고 판매자
DAM YE-JIN HIT'S SECOND TOP SELLER FOR 2024
담예진 2024년 HIT의 두 번째 최고 판매자
This business
이 사업
is pretty cruel,
꽤 잔인해,
don't you think?
그렇지 않은 것 같나요?
Sales aren't everything.
매출이 전부는 아닙니다.
But they use photo size to show the difference.
하지만 그들은 사진 크기를 사용합니다 차이점을 보여드리기 위해.
I heard you almost made a scene again.
또 다시 한 번 소동을 벌일 뻔했다고 들었습니다.
I actually did.
실제로 그랬어요.
We sold 230% of our target.
목표의 230%를 매도했습니다.
That's a huge scene.
엄청난 장면이군요.
But you're a pro in that area.
하지만 당신은 그 분야의 프로입니다.
I bring in more with one jar of cream than you do with ten rags.
크림 한 병으로 더 많이 가져오네 넝마 열 개로 하는 것보다
Right.
오른쪽.
While you sell one, I sell ten.
당신이 한 개를 파는 동안 나는 열 개를 팔아요.
What?
무엇?
Isn't it a relief that I don't sell cosmetics?
위로가 되지 않나 내가 화장품을 안 판다고?
Look here, Dam Ye-jin.
여기 봐, 담예진.
Hey.
여기요.
We have plans.
우리에겐 계획이 있어요.
See you later.
나중에 봐요.
What's the deal with Ji Yun-ji?
지윤지랑 무슨 사이야?
Geez, she's evil to the bone.
이런, 그녀는 뼛속까지 사악해요.
She insults you instead of being a supportive senior.
그녀는 당신을 모욕합니다 지지해주는 선배가 되기보다는.
Are you being upset on my behalf?
당신이 나를 대신해서 화를 내고 있는 겁니까?
Damn it, I've been upset all day!
젠장, 하루 종일 속상했어!
If you do that to me again on a live broadcast,
또 나한테 그런 짓 하면 생방송 중
regardless of our four-year friendship,
4년간의 우정과는 상관없이,
I'm gone. Got that?
나는 갔다. 알았어?
I got it, so you can stop.
알았으니 그만해도 됩니다.
You don't yell at a woman who just broke up.
여자한테 소리 지르지 마 방금 헤어진 사람.
Why did you get dumped?
왜 버림받았나요?
I never said I got dumped.
나는 버림 받았다고 말한 적이 없습니다.
I mean…
내 말은...
-You're so busy. -So what?
-너무 바쁘군요. -그래서 뭐?
Everyone's busy.
다들 바빠요.
But not everyone lives like you.
하지만 모두가 당신처럼 사는 것은 아닙니다.
How do other people live then?
그러면 다른 사람들은 어떻게 살아요?
You know,
있잖아,
I work to eat chicken and beer after clocking out.
나는 치킨과 맥주를 먹기 위해 일한다 퇴근 후.
I smile when I think about chicken and beer,
생각하면 웃는다 치킨과 맥주에 대해
and I can endure any crap that people give me.
그리고 난 어떤 쓰레기라도 견딜 수 있어 사람들이 나에게 주는 것.
That's what helps me breathe.
그것이 내가 숨을 쉬는 데 도움이 되는 것입니다.
Everyone has something like that.
누구나 그런 것이 있습니다.
A lover, a celebrity they like, a hobby,
연인, 좋아하는 연예인, 취미,
or maybe just a restaurant they like.
아니면 그냥 그들이 좋아하는 레스토랑일 수도 있습니다.
But you?
하지만 당신은?
You just never clock out of work.
당신은 결코 퇴근하지 않습니다.
Well, it just happens that when I'm working--
글쎄요, 그냥 그런 일이 일어나는 거죠 내가 일할 때--
Exactly. So why are you working?
정확히. 그럼 왜 일하고 있나요?
Don't we all work to live a decent life?
우리 모두는 품위 있는 삶을 살기 위해 노력하고 있지 않습니까?
But do you know why I still make time to date?
그런데 왜 그런지 아시나요 아직도 데이트할 시간이 있나요?
Because I have a personal life.
개인적인 삶이 있기 때문이죠.
I want to live like a human being.
나는 인간처럼 살고 싶다.
I just want to laugh and enjoy my time with you.
난 그냥 웃고 싶어 그리고 당신과 함께 즐거운 시간을 보내세요.
But with you, Dam Ye-jin.
하지만 담예진님과 함께라면요.
Not home shopping host Dam Ye-jin.
홈쇼핑 호스트 담예진이 아닙니다.
DOESN'T CUT WELL ENOUGH
충분히 잘리지 않아
PASTEL POPULAR AMONG THE YOUNG
젊은이들 사이에서 인기 있는 파스텔
My daughter, Ye-jin. Your health is the most important thing.
내 딸 예진이. 당신의 건강 가장 중요한 것입니다.
No matter how busy you are, make sure to eat well.
아무리 바빠도 식사를 잘 하세요.
Hey, I was checking the responses for the previous Airix product.
아, 답변 확인 중이었는데 이전 Airix 제품의 경우.
And for the new one, I thought…
그리고 새로운 것에 대해서는…
Okay, I'll check that right now.
알겠습니다. 지금 바로 확인해 보겠습니다.
Well… Next week…
음... 다음주에...
I don't think I'll be available next week.
다음 주에는 시간이 없을 것 같아요.
How about the week after that, on the 29th?
그 다음 주는 어떻습니까? 29일?
I only have one meeting at 3:00 p.m., so I can make time in the morning.
오후 3시에 딱 한 번만 회의가 있는데, 그래서 아침에 시간을 낼 수 있어요.
POEMS BY PARK JOON
박준의 시
That's hot.
정말 덥네요.
The wavy rubber tip at the top of the nozzle…
물결 모양의 고무 팁 노즐 상단에…
It's suitable for all hair types, but especially great for straight hair.
모든 모발 타입에 적합하며, 하지만 특히 직모에 좋습니다.
TAKE ONLY WHEN UNABLE TO SLEEP
잠이 오지 않을 때만 복용하세요
GOJEUNEOK BIO
고제억바이오
Do you
당신은
really want to see me lose it?
내가 지는 걸 정말 보고 싶어?
I'm nothing
난 아무것도 아니야
without you or money.
너도 돈도 없이.
Are you trying to make me the villain?
날 악당으로 만들려고 하는 거야?
-I said I don't need it. -Just use it, will you?
- 필요없다고 했어요. -그냥 써볼까?
So I have to just because you tell me to?
그럼 당신이 하라고 해서 내가 그래야만 하는 건가요?
I won't.
나는하지 않을 것이다.
Just use the new one. It'll be nice to ride one with a new engine.
그냥 새것을 사용하세요. 좋을거야 새 엔진으로 타는 것.
I hate loud things.
나는 시끄러운 것을 싫어합니다.
Tractors are supposed to be loud.
트랙터는 소리가 크다고 합니다.
I thought you'd like it.
나는 당신이 그것을 좋아할 것이라고 생각했습니다.
I swear, you're so difficult…
맹세코, 당신은 너무 어려운 사람이에요…
-If that's it, I'm hanging up. -Wait.
-그렇다면 끊겠습니다. -잠깐.
About that thing…
그 일에 대해서…
So you haven't changed your mind?
그럼 마음은 변하지 않았나요?
No. Go ahead as planned.
아니요. 계획대로 진행하세요.
It's hard covering up the bags under your eyes today.
덮는게 힘들어 오늘 눈 밑에 있는 가방들.
Are you tired?
피곤해요?
No, I'm at full power right now.
아니요, 저는 지금 최대 전력을 사용하고 있습니다.
That's Beauty Song's new product, isn't it?
뷰티송이에요 새 제품 아닌가요?
Yes, I bought it since it was going viral.
네, 입소문이 나서 샀어요.
It's awesome. Just look.
굉장해요. 그냥보세요.
Your skin looks silky smooth.
피부가 매끄럽게 보입니다.
It's good.
좋다.
Sir, is this centered?
선생님, 이게 중앙인가요?
-Left? Right? Okay. -Good.
-왼쪽? 오른쪽? 좋아요. -좋은.
Can you place that in the center?
그걸 중앙에 놓을 수 있나요?
Hello.
안녕하세요.
DAM YE-JIN'S ONLY1
담예진의 ONLY1
EMPLOYEES ONLY
직원 전용
Hang on.
잠깐만요.
You smoke, Mr. Hwang?
담배를 피우시나요, 황 선생님?
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Nervous about your first prime time show?
첫 번째 프라임 타임 쇼에 대해 긴장되시나요?
-Well… -I understand.
-글쎄… - 이해해요.
Being a merchandiser is tough.
상인이 되는 것은 힘든 일이다.
People say the "MD" in merchandiser means "must do everything."
사람들은 머천다이저에서 "MD"라고 말해요 "모든 것을 해야 한다"는 뜻이다.
And they say if you're an MD at HIT,
그리고 당신이 HIT의 MD라면,
it means "You're making me crazy, Dam Ye-jin."
그것은 "당신이 나를 미치게 만들고 있어요. 담예진."
Spill it! What's the matter?
쏟으세요! 무슨 일이야?
WEEKLY BROADCAST SCHEDULE
주간 방송 일정
THE JI YUN-JI SHOW
지윤지 쇼
Damn it!
젠장!
How about changing the background color to violet like the brand's color?
배경색을 바꿔보는 건 어때요? 브랜드 컬러처럼 보라색으로?
Violet?
제비꽃?
And…
그리고…
The light might reflect off the products, so please check the angles.
빛이 제품에 반사될 수 있으므로, 그러니 각도를 확인해 보세요.
Ma'am?
부인?
Well…
글쎄… ​​
Did you get the studios wrong?
스튜디오를 잘못 찾으셨나요?
This is the Saturday prime time studio.
이곳은 토요일 프라임타임 스튜디오입니다.
I guess you haven't seen the changed schedule.
아마 당신은 본 적이 없을 것 같아요 변경된 일정.
Tonight's prime time slot has changed to The Ji Yun-ji Show.
오늘 밤의 주요 시간대 지윤지쇼로 변경되었습니다.
We're launching Beauty Song's compact.
뷰티송 컴팩트를 출시합니다.
Beauty Song?
뷰티송?
Yeah.
응.
It seems the set hasn't been cleared yet.
아직 세트가 정리되지 않은 것 같습니다.
Ms. Song.
송 씨.
Ms. Dam didn't see the updated schedule.
Dam 씨는 업데이트된 일정을 보지 못했습니다.
Oh, my.
아, 이런.
You really haven't changed, Ms. Dam.
당신은 정말 변하지 않았어요, 담 씨.
Aren't you sick
아프지 않니
of saying "I didn't know" as an excuse?
"몰랐다"는 변명으로?
-Everyone, I think we should hurry. -Yes, ma'am.
- 여러분, 서둘러야 할 것 같아요. -네, 부인.
-Let's take all these out. -One, two!
- 이것들을 모두 꺼내자. - 하나, 둘!
DAM YE-JIN'S ONLY1
담예진의 ONLY1
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Okay, let's proceed.
좋아, 계속하자.
MAKING ME CRAZY DAM YE-JIN
나를 미치게 만드는 담예진
ANSWER WITHIN TEN SECONDS
10초 이내에 답변해 주세요
Don't answer. It'll be a disaster.
대답하지 마세요. 그것은 재앙이 될 것이다.
-Should I turn it off? -No, that would be worse.
- 꺼야 하나? -아니, 그게 더 나쁠 거야.
She wouldn't go straight to the director, would she?
그녀는 똑바로 가지 않을 거야 감독에게, 그녀는 그럴까요?
Come on. Even if she's practically a human bulldozer,
어서 해봐요. 비록 그녀가 실질적으로 인간 불도저
she'd be insane to just barge in there.
그냥 거기에 끼어든다면 그녀는 제정신이 아닐 것이다.
Right?
오른쪽?
I didn't hear you knock.
나는 당신이 노크하는 것을 듣지 못했습니다.
You're the one who skipped protocol first.
프로토콜을 먼저 건너뛴 건 당신이군요.
Why was the schedule changed to The Ji Yun-ji Show?
일정이 변경된 이유 지윤지쇼?
How could you do this without even telling me?
어떻게 이런 일을 할 수 있었나요? 나한테도 말하지 않고?
At this rate,
이 속도에서는
we'll be crushed by CT Life Shopping before the next quarter.
우리는 CT Life Shopping에 의해 무너질 것이다 다음 분기 전에.
Beauty Song's Song Myeong-hwa Compact
뷰티송의 송명화 콤팩트
was the one that boosted CT's sales.
CT의 매출을 증대시킨 것은 바로 이것이었습니다.
So if they're coming to us,
그러니 그들이 우리에게 온다면,
shouldn't we offer our prime time slot on Saturday?
우리가 제안하면 안 될까? 토요일에 우리 황금 시간대?
Why does it have to be my slot?
왜 내 슬롯이어야 합니까?
The prime time slot
황금 시간대
is for best-selling products,
는 베스트셀러 제품을 위한 것입니다.
not for hosts who have good sales.
매출이 좋은 호스트에게는 적합하지 않습니다.
You know that beauty products are the real moneymakers.
아시다시피 뷰티 제품은 진짜 돈벌이들이야.
Ma'am,
부인,
our team's average target achievement rate for the past three months is over 180%.
우리 팀의 평균 목표 달성률 최근 3개월간 180%가 넘었습니다.
And with prime time consumers,
그리고 황금 시간대 소비자의 경우
we'll be able to show even better results…
더 좋은 결과 보여드릴 수 있겠네요…
That's right.
좋아요.
It's the brand that both Haeseong Duty Free and Lux Duty Free
둘 다 쓰는 브랜드인데 해성면세점과 럭스면세점
were desperate to get on board
탑승하고 싶어 필사적으로 노력했어
but failed to in the end.
하지만 결국 실패했다.
L'Étoile.
레투알.
We'll need a brand like that to push out Beauty Song.
우리에겐 그런 브랜드가 필요하다 뷰티송을 밀어내기 위해.
I don't sell cosmetics.
저는 화장품을 판매하지 않습니다.
That clause has always been in my contracts.
그 조항은 항상 내 계약에 있었어.
But I guess you forgot.
그런데 잊어버린 것 같아요.
I'll find a product that is as good as L'Étoile's.
제품을 찾아볼게요 L'Étoile만큼 훌륭해요.
The Danish royal tableware you mentioned before--
덴마크 왕실 식기 당신이 전에 언급한--
You seem mistaken about something.
당신은 뭔가 착각하고 있는 것 같습니다.
But L'Étoile is the only brand
하지만 L'Étoile이 유일한 브랜드입니다
that would allow you to retake the prime time slot.
그게 당신을 허용할 것입니다 프라임 타임 슬롯을 다시 차지합니다.
If you can't do that,
그렇게 할 수 없다면
then your dream of hosting a show with your name on it will end here.
그렇다면 쇼를 진행하는 꿈을 꾸세요 당신의 이름은 여기서 끝나겠습니다.
-Ma'am! -When are you going to stop running away?
- 부인! - 언제쯤 도망을 그만둘 건가요?
Are you going to betray
배신할 건가요
the partner companies, merchandisers, and producers relying on you over this?
파트너사, 판매자, 그리고 프로듀서들이 이것에 대해 당신에게 의존하고 있습니까?
The next time you enter my office,
다음에 당신이 내 사무실에 들어오면,
you'd better have a contract with L'Étoile.
너는 갖는 것이 좋겠다 L'Étoile과 계약을 맺었습니다.
Ms. Dam.
담 씨.
Have you lost your mind?
정신을 잃었나요?
How could you barge in there like that?
어떻게 그런 곳에 끼어들 수 있었나요?
So what did the director say?
그럼 감독님은 뭐라고 하셨어요?
What is it? What did she say?
그것은 무엇입니까? 그녀가 뭐라고 말했습니까?
She said that if I want my spot back,
그녀는 내가 내 자리를 되찾고 싶다면
I have to bring L'Étoile on board.
L'Étoile을 탑승시켜야 해요.
-L'Étoile? -What?
-레투알? -무엇?
You mean the French brand, L'Étoile?
프랑스 브랜드 L'Étoile 말씀하시는 건가요?
But Ms. Dam doesn't do cosmetics.
그런데 담씨는 화장품을 안 해요.
That hurts.
아프다.
Damn it. How can Ms. Dong be so cruel?
젠장. 동 씨는 어떻게 그렇게 잔인할 수 있나요?
Wait!
기다리다!
How in the world is she going to bring in L'Étoile?
세상에 어떻게 그녀는 L'Étoile을 가져올 예정인가요?
I know.
알아요.
It's not like I'm a celebrity or anything.
제가 연예인이라던가 그런 건 아니에요.
If word gets out that you're in Korea,
당신이 한국에 있다는 소식이 알려지면
the duty-free retailers who sent in offers will be all over you.
면세점 제안을 보낸 사람은 당신에게 전부일 것입니다.
Then, our confidential information would be exposed in no time.
그렇다면 우리의 기밀 정보는 금새 노출될 겁니다.
Look, no one in Korea would recognize me…
봐봐, 한국에서는 나를 알아보는 사람이 아무도 없을 거야…
Where are we going?
우리는 어디로 가는 걸까요?
What's trending in Korea these days?
요즘 한국의 트렌드는 무엇인가요?
First, let me take you to your hotel.
먼저, 호텔로 데려가겠습니다.
You can rest there until your evening meeting.
거기서 쉬면 돼 저녁 회의까지.
You don't mean tonight, do you?
오늘 밤을 뜻하는 건 아니겠죠?
I do, sir.
그렇습니다.
But I just got here from France.
하지만 저는 프랑스에서 막 여기로 왔어요.
Well, the meeting is what you came here for.
글쎄, 회의 당신이 여기 온 목적이 바로 그것입니다.
Did you say the raw material supplier was called Gojeuneok Bio?
원자재 공급업체라고 하셨나요? 고즈억바이오라고 하던데요?
Yes.
예.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Kang Mu-won, CEO of Gojeuneok Bio.
만나서 반가워요. 고즈억바이오 대표 강무원 입니다.
Hello. I'm Eric Seo, Executive Director at L'Étoile.
안녕하세요. 저는 에릭 서입니다. L'Étoile의 전무이사.
Nice to meet you. Please take a seat.
만나서 반가워요. 자리에 앉으세요.
We offered very favorable terms in the new raw material supply contract.
우리는 매우 유리한 조건을 제안했습니다 새로운 원자재 공급 계약을 체결했습니다.
Have you considered it?
고려해 보셨나요?
CONTRACT AMENDMENT PROPOSAL
계약 수정 제안
Of course. I considered it very carefully.
물론. 나는 그것을 매우 신중하게 고려했습니다.
Then--
그 다음에--
But I won't be able to give the answer you want.
하지만 난 줄 수 없을 거야 당신이 원하는 대답.
I'm sorry you had to come all this way.
이렇게까지 오시게 해서 미안해요.
To be honest,
솔직히 말하면,
this is hard to understand.
이것은 이해하기 어렵습니다.
We increased the previous order volume by five times,
늘렸습니다 이전 주문량을 5배로 늘린
and we also adjusted the terms to be much more favorable to Gojeuneok Bio.
그리고 우리는 또한 다음과 같이 조건을 조정했습니다. 고즈억바이오에 훨씬 유리하다.
You're worried you won't be able to manage
당신은 관리할 수 없을까 봐 걱정하고 있어요
-the increased volume, right? -Yes.
-볼륨이 늘어났죠? -예.
Yes, I think that seems to be the biggest concern…
응, 그런 것 같아 가장 큰 걱정거리가 될 것 같아요...
I mean, it is the biggest concern.
즉, 그게 가장 큰 고민이다.
Then,
그러면
we'll come up with a way to resolve that issue.
우리가 방법을 찾아볼게 그 문제를 해결하기 위해.
No,
아니요,
let me be clear about this.
이에 대해 분명히 말씀드리겠습니다.
Gojeuneok Bio
고즈억바이오
will not renew our contract with L'Étoile.
L'Étoile과의 계약을 갱신하지 않습니다.
You must be tired. Should I take you back to the hotel?
피곤하겠네요. 호텔로 다시 데려가야 할까요?
Mr. Cha.
차씨.
There's something strange about Mr. Kang.
강씨는 뭔가 이상한데요.
It was like he was speaking for someone else.
그 사람이 말하는 것 같았어요 다른 사람을 위해.
Then I'll look into Gojeuneok Bio a bit more.
그럼 고즈억바이오에 대해서 알아볼게요 조금 더.
My sister must be worried sick that I'm slacking off here.
누나는 걱정이 많겠구나 내가 여기서 느슨하게 지내고 있다고요.
Our deputy CEO, Michelle, is especially worried about you.
우리의 부회장 미셸(Michelle)은 특히 당신이 걱정됩니다.
Oh, dear. It's raining.
이런. 비가 온다.
We should get this done quickly
이 일을 빨리 끝내야 해
before it's too late.
너무 늦기 전에.
The first set has sold out.
첫 번째 세트가 매진되었습니다.
Oh, my!
아, 이런!
It's sold out. My gosh!
매진되었습니다. 맙소사!
It's already sold out.
이미 매진되었습니다.
You know, it's only been 30 minutes since we started the show.
알다시피, 이제 겨우 30분밖에 안 남았습니다 쇼를 시작한 이후로.
We have an hour, but it's already sold out. At this rate…
한 시간 남았습니다. 근데 이미 매진됐어요. 이대로라면…
All right!
괜찮은!
Since it's late, how about a late-night snack--
시간이 늦어서, 야식은 어때요--
What? So we can watch her show?
무엇? 그럼 우리가 그녀의 쇼를 볼 수 있을까요?
What do we do with our remaining time?
남은 시간에 무엇을 하나요?
Why isn't this turning off? Damn it!
이거 왜 안 꺼지나요? 젠장!
I am so surprised too.
나도 너무 놀랐다.
Just go home now.
이제 집에 가세요.
Right.
오른쪽.
I don't even want to be
난 그렇게 되고 싶지도 않아
in the same building as Ji Yun-ji right now.
같은 건물에 지금 지윤지처럼.
Get up.
일어나세요.
What's really surprising is
정말 놀라운 점은
that blotting paper doesn't seem to stick to this at all.
그 압지 이것을 전혀 고수하지 않는 것 같습니다.
-Right. -If I put a sheet
-그렇습니다. -시트를 넣으면
of blotting paper on my face…
얼굴에 압지...
Look. Seriously.
보세요. 진심으로요.
It just falls off right away.
그냥 바로 떨어져요.
ACTRESS SONG MYEONG-HWA'S BEAUTY SONG COMPACT
배우 송명화의 뷰티송 컴팩트
-We demand compensation!
-배상을 요구합니다!
WE SUFFER EVERY DAY
우리는 매일 고통을 겪는다
I'm sorry. I apologize.
죄송합니다. 사과드립니다.
My skin feels so moist.
피부가 너무 촉촉한 느낌이에요.
I gave away all of my blotting paper to my friends and acquaintances.
압지 전부 나눠줬어요 내 친구와 지인들에게.
-Really? -Yes, seriously.
-정말요? -네, 진심으로요.
I see.
알겠습니다.
As time passes by,
시간이 지날수록
we want to make our skin smooth and gentle.
우리는 피부를 매끄럽게 만들고 싶습니다 부드럽습니다.
When you get to your forties, fifties, and sixties…
40대가 되면 50년대, 60년대...
Stick with your usual size.
평소 사이즈를 유지하세요.
Customer 8782 is asking about washing it.
고객 8782님이 세탁에 관해 문의하셨습니다.
That's why we prepared oil directly imported from Italy.
그래서 우리가 준비한 거야 이탈리아에서 직수입한 오일입니다.
Even if you put it in the washing machine…
세탁기에 넣어도...
I'll discuss it with them right away.
즉시 그들과 논의하겠습니다.
The lineup is made up of these three…
라인업은 이 세가지로 구성되어 있는데...
Ms. Dam, you've already hit the maximum dose and duration.
담 선생님, 당신은 이미 맞았어요 최대 복용량과 기간.
If you keep overusing sleeping pills,
수면제를 계속 남용하면
you may experience serious side effects,
심각한 부작용이 발생할 수 있습니다.
such as sleepwalking, memory loss, and even respiratory depression.
몽유병, 기억 상실 등 심지어 호흡곤란도 발생합니다.
You could seriously hurt yourself.
심각한 부상을 입을 수 있습니다.
Just one pill per day. Please stick to that.
하루에 한 알씩 먹으면 됩니다. 꼭 지켜주세요.
When are you going to stop running away?
도망을 언제쯤 멈출 예정인가요?
Aren't you sick of saying "I didn't know" as an excuse?
아프지 않으셨나요 "몰랐다"는 핑계로
We'll get ready now!
이제 준비하겠습니다!
-Excuse me. -Don't step on that!
-실례합니다. - 밟지 마세요!
Out of the way!
비켜!
Please take this out too.
이것도 꺼내주세요.
-Passing through. -Excuse me.
-통과 중입니다. -실례합니다.
Ms. Dam?
담 씨?
We're starting now. There's no time.
이제 시작하겠습니다. 시간이 없어요.
MS. ANGRY EOM
MS. 화가 나 엄
Ms. Eom, is it another simultaneous live broadcast today?
엄 씨, 또 다른 건가요? 오늘 동시 생방송?
Why isn't she picking up her phone again?
그 사람은 왜 다시 전화를 받지 않는 걸까요?
Is she not here yet?
그 사람 아직 안 왔어요?
This won't do. I'll look for a recorded segment.
이건 안 돼요. 녹화된 부분을 찾아보겠습니다.
You try to do something here.
여기서 뭔가를 하려고 합니다.
-Do what? -Anything.
-무엇을 합니까? -아무것.
-Just do something. -What…
- 그냥 뭐라도 하세요. - 뭐…
Hey! You little…
여기요! 꼬마야...
-Sorry. -Geez.
-죄송합니다. - 이런.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
무슨 일이야? 당신은 아픈가요?
Sorry, I'll go get ready.
미안, 준비하러 갈게.
Hang on. Is something wrong?
잠깐만요. 뭔가 문제가 있나요?
I'm fine.
잘 지내요.
For crying out loud.
큰 소리로 울었기 때문입니다.
I'm really okay.
난 정말 괜찮아요.
We hope all your days are healthy days with Binox.
우리는 당신의 모든 날을 바랍니다 바이녹스와 함께 건강한 하루 보내세요.
Thank you for all of your love and support today.
여러분의 모든 사랑에 감사드립니다. 그리고 오늘 지원하세요.
This was your home shopping host, Dam Ye-jin. Thank you.
이 분은 홈쇼핑 호스트였는데, 담예진. 감사합니다.
Great job!
정말 잘했어요!
You can't focus on just the symptoms.
증상에만 집중할 수는 없습니다.
Real issues and relationships
실제 문제와 관계
that you can't avoid are connected to it.
피할 수 없는 것이 연결되어 있습니다.
There are underlying factors behind your insomnia.
근본적인 요인이 있습니다 당신의 불면증 뒤에.
To break this nightly cycle of insomnia,
밤마다 이어지는 불면증의 악순환을 끊기 위해
you have to resolve the root cause first.
먼저 근본 원인을 해결해야 합니다.
-Goodbye! -Bye!
-안녕히 가세요! -안녕!
It's time to face it now.
이제 그것을 직시할 시간입니다.
You must figure out
당신이 알아내야 합니다
what is deep down inside that's pulling you down.
깊은 곳에 무엇이 있는지 그것이 당신을 실망시키는군요.
Hey, don't joke around.
농담하지 마세요.
-Goodbye. -Bye.
-안녕히 가세요. -안녕.
Get home safely.
집에 안전하게 도착하세요.
Mechoori!
메추리!
-Did you have a good day? -Yeah.
- 좋은 하루 보내셨나요? -응.
Thanks.
감사해요.
-What's this? -Striped maple extract.
-이게 뭐야? -줄무늬 단풍나무 추출물.
I knew you'd never drink it if I told you.
내가 말하면 넌 절대 마시지 않을 거라는 걸 알았어.
I saw you vomiting.
네가 토하는 걸 봤어.
So don't complain and just drink it.
그러니 불평하지 말고 그냥 마시세요.
It helps with stress-related gastritis.
스트레스로 인한 위염에 도움이 됩니다.
I really can't drink it.
저는 정말 못 마시거든요.
You don't have to bring in L'Étoile if you don't want to.
L'Étoile을 가져올 필요는 없습니다. 당신이 원하지 않는다면.
What about our team if I don't?
내가 안 하면 우리 팀은 어쩌지?
If we get fired, we can just go to CT.
해고당하면 그냥 CT로 갈 수 있어요.
Hey, after spending four years
야, 4년을 보낸 후
working with someone who sells everything besides cosmetics,
누군가와 함께 일하기 화장품 외에 모든 것을 파는 사람
I have experience in every field except makeup.
나는 경험이있다 메이크업을 제외한 모든 분야에서요.
You could say I'm an all-rounder.
나는 만능인이라고 말할 수 있습니다.
Do you know what this is?
이게 뭔지 아세요?
Four years ago, after our first show,
4년 전 첫 공연 이후
you left this product description behind in the studio.
이 제품 설명을 남겼습니다 스튜디오 뒤에 있어요.
I think we reached only about 30% of our target rate.
내 생각엔 우리가 도달한 것 같아 목표 비율의 약 30%에 불과합니다.
Remember how we totally messed up?
우리가 어떻게 완전히 엉망이 됐는지 기억나?
I wondered if it was a mistake working with you,
혹시 실수였나 싶었는데 당신과 함께 일해요
but the moment I saw that, I felt relieved.
그런데 그걸 본 순간, 나는 안도감을 느꼈다.
I knew if you were this dedicated, I could trust you.
나는 당신이 이렇게 헌신적인 사람인지 알았습니다. 나는 당신을 믿을 수 있습니다.
But now,
하지만 지금은
you sell over 200% of our target rates.
귀하는 목표 가격의 200% 이상을 판매하고 있습니다.
Seriously, aren't you proud?
정말로, 자랑스럽지 않나요?
What are you trying to say?
무슨 말을 하려는 걸까요?
There are a lot of people who trust you now.
사람이 많아요 지금 당신을 믿는 사람.
So you should trust yourself too.
그러니 당신도 자신을 믿어야 한다.
There's still so much left.
아직 너무 많이 남았습니다.
That's my sister, right?
저 사람은 내 여동생이지, 그렇지?
No, it isn't.
아니요, 그렇지 않습니다.
I'm not sure if you've heard,
들어보셨는지 잘 모르겠습니다.
but the biggest home shopping company in Korea is called HIT.
하지만 가장 큰 홈쇼핑 회사는 한국에서는 HIT라고 합니다.
It's been consistently sending in offers since last year.
꾸준히 그랬어요 작년부터 제안을 보냈습니다.
I know HIT. They contacted you?
나는 히트를 안다. 그 사람들이 당신한테 연락했어요?
Yes, it's a host named Dam Ye-jin…
네, 담예진이라는 진행자입니다…
Who?
WHO?
Home shopping host Dam Ye-jin.
홈쇼핑 호스트 담예진.
It seems like HIT found out that you're in Korea.
HIT가 알아낸 것 같아 당신이 한국에 있다는 걸요.
-She's asking for a meeting. -Set it up as soon as possible.
-그녀가 회의를 요청하고 있어요. -최대한 빨리 설정하세요.
What? But, sir, we still have to deal with the renewal contract--
무엇? 하지만 선생님, 아직 해결해야 할 일이 있어요 갱신 계약으로--
Mr. Cha, I've been stuck here looking at papers for a whole week.
차 선생님, 제가 여기 갇혀 있었어요 일주일 내내 신문을 본다.
Don't you understand how desperate I am
내가 얼마나 절박한지 이해 못하겠어
to just talk to someone?
그냥 누군가랑 얘기하려고?
Don't you?
그렇지 않나요?
Hi…
안녕하세요...
I mean, hello.
내 말은, 안녕하세요.
Nice to meet you. I'm home shopping host Dam Ye-jin.
만나서 반가워요. 홈쇼핑 호스트 담예진 입니다.
I like the proposal.
나는 그 제안을 좋아한다.
Did you read through it carefully?
주의 깊게 읽어보셨나요?
Of course. You did too, right?
물론. 당신도 그랬죠?
Our meeting was scheduled in a hurry, so you could've missed something.
우리 모임은 급하게 예정되어 있었는데, 그래서 뭔가를 놓쳤을 수도 있어요.
Please take another good look.
한 번 더 잘 살펴보시기 바랍니다.
I've already reviewed it thoroughly.
이미 충분히 검토해 봤습니다.
We'll review your proposal with a positive outlook.
귀하의 제안을 검토하겠습니다. 긍정적인 전망으로.
I actually didn't expect our meeting to go so smoothly like this.
사실 우리 만남을 기대하진 않았어 이렇게 순조롭게 갈 수 있게.
I believe HIT has been sending offers to L'Étoile since last year.
HIT가 제안을 보낸 것 같아요 작년부터 L'Étoile에.
So could I ask the reason for this?
그럼 그 이유를 물어봐도 될까요?
Well, we also have one condition.
그런데 우리에게도 조건이 하나 있습니다.
So, you're saying
그럼 당신은
we have to work with you to resolve your raw material renewal contract?
우리는 해결하기 위해 당신과 협력해야 원자재 갱신 계약은요?
Yes. If you can help us resolve this matter,
예. 당신이 우리를 도울 수 있다면 이 문제를 해결해 주세요.
then I'll prioritize HIT's offer
그럼 HIT의 제안을 우선으로 할게요
as soon as I return to France.
프랑스로 돌아가자마자.
Then, I'll take responsibility and solve this matter.
그럼 내가 책임지겠다. 그리고 이 문제를 해결해 보세요.
You're accepting my proposal?
내 제안을 받아들이는 건가요?
Yes, if you promise to come on board right now.
응 약속하면 지금 당장 탑승하세요.
I don't have much time either.
나도 시간이 별로 없어.
Since we don't have much time, why don't we proceed on two fronts?
우리 시간이 별로 없으니까, 왜 우리는 두 가지 전선에서 진행하지 않습니까?
You focus on convincing the CEO of Gojeuneok Bio,
설득력에 중점을 두고 있습니다. 고즈억바이오 대표
and I'll focus on convincing the raw material farm owner.
설득하는 데 집중하겠습니다 원자재 농장주.
The farm owner? Why?
농장주? 왜?
Gojeuneok Bio cultivates their own raw materials.
고즈억바이오가 재배하는 그들 자신의 원료.
If we get the farm owner on our side, we'll have a better advantage negotiating.
농장 주인을 우리 편으로 끌어들이면, 우리는 협상하는 데 더 나은 이점을 갖게 될 것입니다.
By the way…
그런데…
Should we officially exchange numbers now?
이제 정식으로 번호 교환할까요?
Sure.
확신하는.
Here.
여기.
Gosh, my feet.
맙소사, 내 발.
Let's rest a bit.
좀 쉬자.
Oh, my gosh.
아, 이런.
Hey, perfect timing.
아, 타이밍 딱 맞네요.
Hello, Su-min. Give me a ride to the living room.
안녕하세요, 수민님. 거실까지 태워다 주세요.
Pardon?
죄송합니다
-Hey, why are you turning around? -Pardon?
-야, 왜 돌아서는데? -죄송합니다
-Hey!
-여기요! -실례합니다
Hey, Su-min… Hello, Su-min!
안녕하세요 수민님... 안녕하세요 수민님!
-Come here. -Pardon?
-이리 오세요. -죄송합니다
-Hello-- -My name is Su-min.
-안녕하세요-- -제 이름은 수민입니다.
-Hey, Su-min. Come back here. -I am not able to do that.
-안녕, 수민. 여기로 돌아오세요. -저는 그렇게 할 수 없습니다.
Hey, where are you going?
이봐, 어디 가는 거야?
My name is Su-min.
제 이름은 수민입니다.
Fine. Just go.
괜찮은. 그냥 가세요.
Pardon?
죄송합니다
You're out.
당신은 아웃입니다.
I do not understand.
이해가 안 돼요.
What am I doing?
내가 뭘 하고 있는 거지?
-I do not understand what you are saying. -Be quiet.
-무슨 말씀인지 이해가 안 됩니다. - 조용히 하세요.
L'Étoile.
레투알.
Let's see.
어디 보자.
The key ingredient of the essence seems to be WF-Mushroom.
에센스의 핵심성분 WF-Mushroom인 것 같습니다.
Find more data on this.
이에 대한 더 많은 데이터를 찾아보세요.
WF-Mushroom is the key ingredient in La Fin Essence
WF-버섯이 핵심 성분입니다 라핀 에센스
and makes up over 90% of the formula.
공식의 90% 이상을 차지합니다.
It's an extract of the white flower noori mushroom.
추출물입니다 흰꽃누리버섯
Can you explain more about the white flower noori mushroom?
더 자세히 설명해 주실 수 있나요? 흰꽃누리버섯은요?
The white flower noori mushroom is native to Korea,
흰꽃누리버섯 한국이 원산지입니다.
and its extract is known for boosting skin elasticity,
그 추출물도 알려져 있습니다 피부 탄력 증진을 위한
reducing pore size, and providing antioxidant benefits.
모공 크기 감소 항산화 효과를 제공합니다.
I like the data.
나는 데이터를 좋아한다.
You're useful. You get a pass.
당신은 유용합니다. 당신은 패스를 얻습니다.
HIT HOMESHOPPING
히트 홈쇼핑
All done.
모두 완료되었습니다.
You're heading to the farm?
농장으로 가시나요?
Yes, I wanted to check it myself.
네, 직접 확인하고 싶었어요.
What's the exact address?
정확한 주소는 무엇입니까?
We only know that it's in Deokpung Village.
우리만 알죠 덕풍마을에 있다고 하네요.
Then, I'll just go and ask around.
그럼 그냥 가서 물어봐야겠어요.
There can't be many farms that big in the country.
농장이 많을 수는 없다 그 나라에서는 그렇게 큰데.
From here, go straight.
여기에서 직진하세요.
GOODBYE DEOKPUNG VILLAGE EXIT
안녕 덕풍마을 출구
Oh, no. I can't move over.
안 돼. 나는 움직일 수 없다.
Sir, let me pass.
선생님, 지나가게 해주세요.
Can you move your vehicle?
차량을 이동할 수 있나요?
What's with him?
그 사람은 뭐야?
Hey! I said move your car!
여기요! 내가 차를 옮기라고 했어!
It seems like you're not from around here.
당신은 이 근처 출신이 아닌 것 같습니다.
But here, we have things called rules.
하지만 여기에는 규칙이라는 것이 있습니다.
This is a one-way street.
이것은 일방통행 거리입니다.
I've come much further in. I have the right of way.
나는 훨씬 더 안쪽으로 들어왔다. 나에게는 통행우선권이 있다.
This is the way out.
이것이 탈출구입니다.
Whoever can back up faster should move. Can't you see this?
더 빨리 백업할 수 있는 사람은 움직여야 합니다. 이걸 볼 수 없나요?
Tractors can't reverse.
트랙터는 후진할 수 없습니다.
How can tractors not reverse? Don't be ridiculous.
트랙터는 어떻게 후진하지 않을 수 있나요? 말도 안되는 소리하지 마십시오.
I'm not being ridiculous.
나는 말도 안되는 소리가 아닙니다.
This tractor can't reverse because it fell into a ditch.
이 트랙터는 후진할 수 없습니다. 수렁에 빠졌기 때문입니다.
Because it fell into a ditch?
도랑에 빠졌기 때문에?
Then, this convertible can't reverse either
그렇다면 이 컨버터블은 어느 쪽도 되돌릴 수 없어
because that's uncool!
그건 쿨하지 못하니까!
SOLD OUT ON YOU
당신은 매진되었습니다
THANKS TO SPECIAL GUEST PARK JI-HWAN
특별 게스트 박지환님에게 감사드립니다
What happened to your ear?
귀에 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
If you keep loitering, I'll report you for obstructing business.
계속 배회한다면 업무방해죄로 신고하겠습니다.
That tractor!
그 트랙터!
You're not putting her in charge of cosmetics again, are you?
당신은 그녀에게 책임을 맡길 수 없습니다 또 화장품 얘기야?
I'm Dam Ye-jin. I don't back out once I've made up my mind.
담예진입니다. 나는 물러서지 않는다 결정을 내리면.
Darling! Hurry and grab the chickens.
여보! 서둘러서 닭을 잡아보세요.
Hey, Changsik!
안녕, 창식!
-Why did you come here? -I'm here for one thing.
-여기 왜 오셨나요? -저는 한 가지 목적으로 여기 왔습니다.
Make an official appointment.
공식적인 약속을 잡으세요.
Instead of that, I'll do it my way.
대신 내 방식대로 할게요.
Is this the way you were talking about?
이것이 당신이 말한 방식인가요?
My goodness!
이럴 수가!
What's your deal?
당신의 거래는 무엇입니까?
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park
자막 번역: 박주영